spacetimestudios.com 2016-11-24

# Spacetime Studios - Spacetime Studios Privacy Policy

Spacetime Studios, Inc. ("Spacetime" "we" "our" or "us") is a digital games development studio and offers users its electronic games and other related online or offline information, services and products to support the games. These highlights detail important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on our websites, successor websites, mobile websites, applications and related services and tools that link to this Privacy Policy when you interact with Spacetime or its products or services by any method (collectively, "Services"). We provide this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue to use the Services and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to the use of the Services. Please read our full Privacy Policy for details and defined terms. 

**Spacetime Studios Legal and Privacy Information**

**Effective Date: March 11, 2015**

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY ("PRIVACY POLICY") CAREFULLY AND IN ITS ENTIRETY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITES, APPLICATIONS OR ANY OTHER SPACETIME PRODUCTS OR SERVICES.**

Spacetime Studios Inc.("Spacetime, "we" "us", "our"), has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on the our website, successor websites, mobile website and applications, and related products and services, and tools that link to this Privacy Policy as well as when you interact with Spacetime or its products or services by any method of communications such as email, in person, etc. (collectively, "Services"). It does not apply to sites or tools maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and you should read those privacy policies carefully. Spacetime provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue to use the Services and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to the use of the Services. Each time that you access or use Services, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. 

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR TERMS OF USE WHICH GOVERN YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES, PLEASE DISCONTINUE ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICES.**   

* * *

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Information You Provide To Us.** You can browse our Services without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. However, we will collect personal information from you, when you create or update your account or profile, during online game play, while interacting with other users, use various features of our Services, such as in game purchases, or other goods or services or communicate directly with us. We may combine that information with other information collected from the devices you use to access our Services, such as your operating system type or mobile device model, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. We may also collect information about the website you visited before you came to our Services and the website you visit after you leave our Services, if this information is supplied to us by your browser.

**Your Imported Profile from Social Networks.** When using our Services and third-party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google +) (each and collectively, a "Social Network"), you may have the option to consent to connecting your profile or activity on our Services with your Social Network information and activity. If you choose to use our Social Network populating feature to create an account we may import personal and non-identifiable information for your account or profile on our Services from another Social Network. We only import from the information you allow to be imported from the Social Network which is controlled by your privacy settings on that Social Network ("Permitted Social Network Content"). The authentication of your Social Network login credentials are conducted solely by the Social Network If you do use this feature, we will initially create your profile by displaying information such as your first name as the user name, biography, location, interests, occupation, and email address. By associating your Social Network account with our Services and authorizing us to have access to this information, you agree that we may post on Facebook on your behalf, and we may collect, use, and store Permitted Social Network Content across all our Services and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Surveys and Promotions.** From time to time we may request information from you and other users via surveys or contests or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys, contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary. Contact information may be used as set forth in this policy and as set forth in the official rules to notify the winners and award prizes and file winners’ information as required by law. Survey information will be used for the purposes of the survey.

**Information You Post on Forums.** The Services are designed to enable you to communicate with others. Any information or content you post when participating with the Services and Social Networks, plug ins or other applications becomes public information, depending upon your privacy settings, and is subject to redistribution by Spacetime and other third parties. There is no expectation of privacy when posting content or otherwise participating in online chat rooms, blogs, message boards, user "profiles" for public view or in similar interactive forums on our Services or third party services ("Forums") and we have no control over how those users may use the information you make public. Therefore, you should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting.

**Mobile/Location Information.** We may collect additional information from you if you access Services through a mobile device, for example your unique device identifier, IP address, language, locale, device’s operating system, location or geo-location. When you use our Services we may request your permission to collect your location information. Please be advised some features will not be available if you choose not to provide your location data to us. However, the degree to which your location can be identified depends on the device you are using (e.g. laptop, smartphone, tablet) and how you are connected to the Internet (e.g. via cable broadband connection, Wi-Fi, etc.). If you enable location services for our Services, we may collect location data periodically as you use or leave open our Services. We may also use this data internally or in conjunction with our third-party service providers to customize your experience and provide offers that may be relevant to you. Depending on the platform you use to access our Services (e.g., Apple, iOS, Google, Android, Windows, etc.), you may be able to control from within the settings on your wireless device or the Services whether location data is collected.

**Information about Others/Inviting Friends.** Our Services may provide the ability for you to submit personal information about other people such as their name and email address to invite them to join a Service. Inviting friends is always optional. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Services, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend so select your friends carefully. Use of friend finder third party tools are available through our Services and can help you find your contacts; however, please be aware that if you use those tools, those friends may be able to associate your account information with your social networking profile and/or email address.

**Information from Other Sources.** The information we collect may be combined with information from outside records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, additional contact information) that we have acquired in accordance with the law.

**Billing information.** In accessing certain areas through the Services (such as co-branded or third party branded locations on the Services), you may be requested by third party payment processors such as PayPal, Amazon, iTunes and Google Pay to provide additional information in order to complete a purchase such as your name, address and billing information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to and we cannot control the activities of any third party processors and you should consult the respective privacy policies of any third parties when accessing their services through the Services. 

* * *

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

Our goal is to collect and use only that information that we think is required for our legitimate business interests, to better understand your interests, and to improve your experience of using the Services.

**Usage Information.** In addition to any personal information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we and our business partners may use a variety of tracking technologies that automatically (or passively) collect certain information described in this Privacy Policy from your computer, mobile, or other access device whenever you visit or interact with the Services or our advertising ("Usage Information").Usage information may be combined with personal information We use tracking technologies (including cookies) to collect Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including:

  * Operationally Necessary. We may use tracking technologies required for system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security or allow you to make use of shopping cart functionality, determining applicable tax rates. We may also collect user names and password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and/or connection information.  

  * Performance-Related. We may use cookies or other tracking technologies to assess the performance of our Services, including as part of our analytic practices to improve the content or functionality offered through the Services.  

  * Functionality-Related. We may use tracking technologies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited the Services before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest. This information may also include game play statistics, feature usage, scores and achievements, rankings, and click paths.  

  * Targeting-Related. We may use tracking technologies to deliver content, including our ads, relevant to your interests on our Services and third-party websites and online services based on how you interact with our advertisements or content as well as track the content you access on our Services and elsewhere. For further information on this, and your opt-out choices, click here.  

  * Keep in mind that certain features of our Services are available only through the use of tracking technologies and disabling them may impact on the functionality of our Services. For further information on disabling tracking technologies, click here.  

**Third-Party Tracking.** You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third-party service providers (such as Google Analytics) that assist us with various aspects of our operations and Services and provide us with information about your interests based on your web viewing on other sites or applications. You may find more information about these third parties and their practices and your choices on how such data is collected by clicking here. In addition, our Services may contain links, widgets, advertising, etc. linking to third-party websites, applications or products. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties and we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website that collects personal information from you.

**Game Play.** When you are playing our games or otherwise using the Services, your game-play behavior, player stats, and purchasing, if applicable, as well as other information may be monitored. We may also monitor your device information for third party programs that interact with our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of any third parties and you should consult the respective privacy policies regarding how they use your information. 

* * *

**3\. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

**Use of Information by Us.** We may use Information that we collect about you: (1) to use or to share with our service providers to fulfill your requests or orders and respond to your requests (2) to provide customer service, resolve disputes, problems with your account or our Services or administer a sweepstakes or promotion (3) to improve our Services and to customize your experience and the content and advertising; (4) to give you information about your account or our Services; (5) for ad servers or networks; (6) for internal business purposes; and (7) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Co-branded Areas.** Certain areas on our Services may be provided to you in association with third parties who often provide us specialized content, native advertising ( a form of advertising that matches the form and function of the Service on which it appears), or offer products or services ("Co-Branded Areas"). Such Co-Branded Areas will identify directly or indirectly the third party. If you elect to interact with or register for the products and/or services provided at these Co-Branded Areas, you either will be providing your personal information to both us and the third party or we might be providing your personal information directly to the third party. Your personal information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties and we suggest you review the respective privacy policies of those third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

**Interacting with Other Users.** Your user name, picture, biography, interests, and time zone will be displayed or stored so you can play/interact with other users, and use various interactive features of our Services.

**Sharing With Affiliates and Marketing Partners.** We may share your personal information and other information we collect from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy with our affiliated companies and marketing partners to send you messages about new products, enhancements, special offers, contests, sweepstakes, events, surveys, and other promotions.

**Connecting with Social Networks.** If this option is available and you permit a connection between a Social Network and any of our Services that enable a connection with a Social Network, that Social Network may be able to identify you and to associate information received from the connection with information the Social Network already has about you. Please review the Social Network’s privacy policy and choices for sharing information of any Social Network connected to our Services. If you authorize a connection from our Services to a Social Network you permit us to share or publish information about your activity on our Services, with that Social Network and its users, and to access Permitted Social Network Content. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to: technical information about your Services activities and content, including videos, which you access on our Services. Information we may access about you, subject to your privacy settings on the Social Network, may include your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers, and certain of your activities on the Social Network.

**Advertising.** We use third-party ad servers and ad networks that use tracking technology to collect information about your visits on other services and when you access our Services to send you targeted advertisements. Some dynamic in-game advertisement serving technology enable advertising to be temporarily uploaded into your game, web browser or mobile device and replaced while you are online. These third parties may use personal and non-personally identifiable information collected from your device (such as IP address or device identifier) to serve advertising and measure and control the cadence and effectiveness of ad delivery. They automatically receive your IP address or mobile device identifier when this happens. They may also use tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of advertisements, personalize the advertising content and serve you advertisements that are relevant to your regional location. We may also use information collected by third party ad servers and networks using third-party cookies and beacons on our Services and in our emails to deliver advertising about our Services displayed to you on third-party services. Google is one of the companies that we use to serve advertising and perform analytics on some of our Services. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Services. This data may be collected, used and disclosed as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the privacy policy of the company who is providing ad serving tracking technology.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of ad servers or ad networks. However, our ad servers and ad networks may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt out of receiving targeted ads on our Services, you may continue to receive advertising and promotional messages, but it will not be customized or personalized to you based on your use of our Services and/or third-party websites or online services. Please note that the opt-out is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer, browser and device on which the opt-out is applied.

If you would like more information about interest based advertising and your choices not to accept cookies used to track your activities go to Ad Choices or you can go to [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). If you would like to learn more about how interest-based information is collected and to know your choices about not having behavioral tracking information used in this manner, you can go to [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Note: Ad serving technologies are integrated into our Services; if you want to be certain that your information is not used for online behavioral tracking, do not play our games or use the Services.**

**Browser Do Not Track Signals.** Some third-party browsers provide "do not track," machine-readable signals for websites and online services that are automatically applied by default. Please note that we endeavor to respect browsers’ do not track requests. Do not track requests are forwarded to relevant third parties. However, we have no control over the information sent from your browser to third parties such as ad networks and analytics companies. We recommend that you check your browser settings to prevent the disclosure of information you would not like to share.

**Analyze and Aggregate Information.** We use aggregate information about our users and other non-personal information to analyze the Services and user behavior and to prepare aggregated reports, which we share with third parties. To learn about our analytics providers’ currently available privacy policies and opt-out options, click here.   
**Communicate With You and Third Parties at Your Request.** We use your information to contact you to send you purchase confirmations and other information to maintain your account, to comply with your stated communication preferences, to provide other Services requested by you, as described at the time when we collect the information from you, or to contact you for purposes authorized by law.

**Mobile/Location Data.** When you access the Services on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as locally based search results, the ability to play or connect with users of our Services in your region and other personalized content.

**Offers and Promotional Messages.** We may use your email address to send you updates and communications about our products and services or our promotional partners’ products or services or other messages, such as newsletters, text messages, when users check-in, changes to features of the Services or special offers. We also might share that information with our promotional partners who may share special offers and discounts with you. You will be given the opportunity in any promotional email that we send to you to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. To see your choice and opt-out options, please contact us at click here.

**Push Notifications.** Our application Services may include a function that allows us to use push notifications to send you updates, communications, and other messages about the Service. To opt out of getting these push notifications or other messages, you must turn off the push notification function within your device settings and within the in-game options menu. We do not send promotional messages about other products or services through these push notifications.

**Legal Matters; Safety.** We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Use, which we encourage you to read in conjunction with this Privacy Policy, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Any disputes under this Privacy Policy will be resolved in accordance with the binding arbitration process outlined in the Terms of Service. Additionally, we may disclose your information in situations that we believe may involve potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property.

**Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets.** If Spacetime or an affiliated company or brand or business is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, personal information of our users may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Information about our users may also need to be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we or any one of our businesses are seeking financing, investment, support or funding.

**Storage and Retention.** Personally identifiable information that you provide to us in the course of requesting a product or service through the Services may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases. We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is permitted or required by law. 

* * *

**4\. ACCESSING AND CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Updating/Changing Your Forum Account Information.** Registered users of Spacetime can review and edit their Forum account information by logging into their Spacetime Forum account and clicking on "settings."

**Updating/Changing Your Game Account information.** You can change or update your game account information by going to the account modification page available in each game. You should promptly update all your accounts if any information changes or becomes inaccurate.

**Assistance.** If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information you provided to us is not correct and you cannot change it by accessing your account, contact us as set forth in Section 7, "Contacting Us".

* * *

**5\. CHOICE AND OPT OUTS**

**Information Sharing with Others.** To make choices about the information received and shared with other account holders go to [support@spacetimestudios.com](mailto:support@spacetimestudios.com). Be aware that any personally identifiable information you disclose in these Forums is publicly available and for instance can be used to send you unsolicited messages.

**Privacy Settings.** Information that you disclose while participating in the Services may be public and subject to redistribution by us and any third party that reviews your profile or information that you post. Please be aware that Spacetime is not responsible for the uses or copies of your public postings on or through Services which are downloaded by third parties.

**Cancelling/Deactivating Your Account.** You may request that we cancel and close your account by contacting customer service at [support@spacetimestudios.com](mailto:support@spacetimestudios.com) or you can deactivate your account by navigating on your phone to uninstall the applicable game. You can remove the connection between Facebook and your account by accessing your Facebook settings, selecting apps, and removing the selected app. When you cancel or deactivate your account, we will retain logs and information about you for the purposes set forth in this privacy policy along with an archival copy of your information which might be used by us for recordkeeping and internal purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service and for demographic, reporting and research purposes. If you cancel or deactivate your account, you will not be able to access any of your personal information.

**Administrative Messages.** You may not opt out of administrative e-mails (for example e-mails about your transactions or policy changes) for your registered account.

**Opting Out of Promotional Messages.** You may choose not to receive our promotional communications by contacting us at for email or other direct mail promotional communications. You may also click the unsubscribe link in the footer of any e-mail or newsletter. You may also e-mail us at [support@spacetimestudios.com](mailto:support@spacetimestudios.com?subject=Opting%20Out%20of%20Promotional%20Messages). It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request.

**Timing and Third Parties.** We will endeavor to comply with your requests as soon as reasonably possible, but please note that changes requested of us may not be effective immediately. Unless required by law, we are not responsible for informing third parties with whom we have already shared your information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities. 

* * *

**6\. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES**

**Permission to Contact You.** When you provide us with information in connection with a particular activity or otherwise sign up for our Services or provide your contact information, including an email address in connection with that activity, product or service, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase or inquiry establishing a business relationship with us. You expressly consent to our communicating with you future information about our Services using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any email address you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, or any other means of communication that your computer, wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving, in accordance with law.

**Links to Other Sites.** To the extent hyperlinks, widgets or similar code may be utilized on our Services to access external or third-party sites or applications, you should be aware that these external or third-party sites are not controlled by us and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of those third-party sites or applications to determine how your personal information will be utilized by the proprietors.

**Security.** We implement security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. However, despite our efforts, no system can completely guarantee that there will never be unauthorized access to your personal information, and your use of the Services indicates that you are willing to assume this risk. We cannot assume responsibility or liability from unauthorized access to our Services or systems.

**Your California Privacy Rights.** California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the "Shine the Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. To make such a request, please contact us at Spacetime [support@spacetimestudios.com](mailto:support@spacetimestudios.com). For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, mail or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly or that do not have complete information.

**Jurisdiction and Cross-Border Issues.** Our Services are available globally and your personal information may be processed in the U.S. and elsewhere. We do not represent or warrant that our Services are appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Services do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit access to our Services, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. By using our Services and submitting any personal information, you consent to the transfer of personal information to other countries, such as the United States, which may provide a level of data security different from your country of residence. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Services.

**Children's Privacy.** The Services are directed to a general audience and we restrict the use of our Services to individuals age 13 and above. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 13 years of age, and if we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years of age, we will take steps to block that child from accessing our Services and/or remove that user’s personal information from our systems. If you become aware that anyone under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us as set forth in Section 7, "Contacting Us".

**No Rights of Third Parties.** This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Services.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Services. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Services via a link, with the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Policy. You should check the Services frequently for updates. By accessing the Services after the Effective Date you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy. 

* * *

**7\. CONTACTING US**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or the practices of Spacetime, please contact us at [support@spacetimestudios.com](mailto:support@spacetimestudios.com?subject=Privac%20%20y%20Policy)   

**Copyright ©2015 Spacetime Studios Inc. All rights reserved.**

* * *

**THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS OF ANALYTICS TOOLS**

This is a nonexclusive list of third parties we have hired to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of the Services, their privacy policies, and, if applicable, opt-out options to enable you to opt out of their respective programs. 

  * **Google**  
<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>
  * **AD-X tracking**  
<http://adxtracking.com/what-we-do>
  * **Facebook**  
<https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms>

* * *

**EXAMPLES OF TRACKING TOOLS**

**Cookies.** A cookie is a data file placed on a device when the device is used to visit the Services. We use cookies to collect information for record-keeping purposes and to make it easier to navigate the Services. Cookies are stored on users’ hard drives. We use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Session ID cookies are used to store information while a user is logged into the Services and expire when the user closes his/her browser. Persistent cookies are used to make tasks like logging into the Services easier for returning users by remembering a user’s login information. Persistent cookies stay on a user’s hard drive from one session to the next. Flash cookies, known as local shared objects, are data files placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built in or downloaded by you to your Device to personalize your visit. Our third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from standard browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including, without limitation, remembering you and your preferences and tracking your visits to our web pages. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a persistent or session cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off such cookies through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. However, cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click [http://www.macromedia.com/support/do...s_manager.html](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). If you choose to disable cookies on your Device, some features of the Services may not function properly.

**Web Beacons/GIFS.** Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as “1×1 GIFs” or “clear GIFs”) may be included in our web pages and messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to our Services, to monitor how users navigate the Services, to count how many sent e-mails were actually opened or to count how many particular articles or links were actually viewed.

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Services, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your device used to access Services from our web server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Services, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

**HTML5.** We use HTML5 in some of our applications, including in our mobile website for the iPhone or iPad. HTML5 has browser web storage that does not rely on traditional browser cookies. Like Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies are not stored in a browser “cookies” file and, like Flash cookies, can be used to track users across websites. To our knowledge there is currently no known way for a user of a mobile device to remove HTML5 tracking and storage.

**e-tags/cache browers/web logs.** Like most standard website servers, we log IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) and device identification in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the Services. We may track your movement within the Services, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. This information may include the browser you are using, the Internet address from which you linked to our Services, the operating system of your computer, the unique IP address of the computer or device identification from the mobile device that you used to access our Services and usage and browsing habits. We use this information in the aggregate to gauge the effectiveness, usage, and popularity of our Services, track information for statistical purposes, help diagnose and troubleshoot server malfunctions, analyze trends, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information. We may also use individual information we collect through web logs to send you targeted offers and other communications.

AD-X Tracking - [https://dashboard.ad-x.co.uk/latest/...td_License.pdf](https://dashboard.ad-x.co.uk/latest/terms/std_License.pdf)  
AdColony - <http://adcolony.com/legal/privacy/>  
Facebook - <https://www.facebook.com/note.php?note_id=+322194465300>  
Flurry - <http://www.flurry.com/about-us/legal/privacy.html>  
Fyber - <https://www.fyber.com/privacypolicy-en.html>  
Google - <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>  
GrowMobile - <http://www.growmobile.com/privacy_policy/>  
Millennial Media - <http://www.millennialmedia.com/privacy-policy/>  
mMedia Platform Policies - <http://mmedia.com/policy>  
Mobile App Tracking - <http://mobileapptracking.com/privacy-policy/>  
NativeX - <http://policy.w3i.com/PrivacyPolicy_Full.html>  
Nanigans - <http://www.nanigans.com/privacy-policy/>  
TapJoy - <http://info.tapjoy.com/about-tapjoy/privacy-policy/>  
Trialpay - <http://www.trialpay.com/legal/privacy-policy/>
